[
    {
        "question": "My father is very ............. He always donates money to many charities.",
        "choices": [
            "miserly",
            "cruel",
            "generous",
            "dirty"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "generous"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salah's skill provides a ............ model for inspiring young people.",
        "choices": [
            "reel",
            "rule",
            "role",
            "roll"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "role"
    },
    {
        "question": "People can ............ to the Egyptian Food Bank to help others.",
        "choices": [
            "donate",
            "steal",
            "support",
            "call"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donate"
    },
    {
        "question": "High blood pressure is considered a ............ disease.",
        "choices": [
            "long-term",
            "medium-term",
            "short-term",
            "first-term"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "long-term"
    },
    {
        "question": "It's too cold and I've no ............ to visit anyone.",
        "choices": [
            "desire",
            "identity",
            "problem",
            "prestige"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "desire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Blood ............ should be measured regularly.",
        "choices": [
            "pleasure",
            "treasure",
            "pressure",
            "donation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "pressure"
    },
    {
        "question": "The child with a diseased kidney will have a transplant, but we are waiting for a ................",
        "choices": [
            "borer",
            "mower",
            "owner",
            "donor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sir Magdi Jacoub's centre for heart in Aswan is famous for heart ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "transports",
            "transplants",
            "plants",
            "planets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "transplants"
    },
    {
        "question": "Good education, money and power  give people ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "prestige",
            "hometown",
            "conservation",
            "monitor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "prestige"
    },
    {
        "question": "First, you need to be checked carefully before blood ............ to make sure you are healthy.",
        "choices": [
            "donate",
            "donor",
            "donation",
            "donated"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donor"
    },
    {
        "question": "He gets much ............ from his brother.",
        "choices": [
            "support",
            "supports",
            "supporter",
            "supported"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "support"
    },
    {
        "question": "We heard a lion ............ , so we returned quickly to the car.",
        "choices": [
            "transplanting",
            "tracking",
            "printing",
            "roaring"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "roaring"
    },
    {
        "question": "The driver paid a fine because he was driving at a very high ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "support",
            "speed",
            "transplant",
            "prestige"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Iron ............ is the amount of iron stored in the body.",
        "choices": [
            "track",
            "clothes",
            "tool",
            "level"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "level"
    },
    {
        "question": "To succeed and reach your goal, you need to be very ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "intelligent",
            "intelligence",
            "stupid",
            "stupidity"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "intelligence"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the suffix which can be added to form the noun from the verb \"agree\"?",
        "choices": [
            "-tion",
            "-ness",
            "-ion",
            "-ment"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "-tion"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed Salah's ............ is \"the Happiness Maker\".",
        "choices": [
            "surname",
            "first name",
            "nickname",
            "pen name"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "nickname"
    },
    {
        "question": "I ............ Aswan in winter as its weather is fantastic then.",
        "choices": [
            "hate",
            "dislike",
            "admire",
            "leave"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "admire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Eight teams play the quarter ............ of a championship.",
        "choices": [
            "rule",
            "final",
            "beginning",
            "role"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "final"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a friend who works in a big company ............ in Kuwait.",
        "choices": [
            "laid",
            "lied",
            "based",
            "basis"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "based"
    },
    {
        "question": "My parents always ............ me when I do well at school.",
        "choices": [
            "praise",
            "apologise",
            "bully",
            "defend"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "praise"
    },
    {
        "question": "It's my father's success at basketball that ............ me to play the game.",
        "choices": [
            "inspired",
            "aspired",
            "conspired",
            "respire"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "inspired"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salah is known as the happiness ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "founders",
            "volunteers",
            "conservationists",
            "maker"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "maker"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unfortunately, the old man died after a short ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "fun",
            "happiness",
            "condition",
            "illness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "illness"
    },
    {
        "question": "It was only later in her life that she found ............ and peace of mind .",
        "choices": [
            "happy",
            "happiness",
            "sad",
            "sadness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "happiness"
    },
    {
        "question": "My father spares no efforts in order to ............ me that having a job would give me prestige.",
        "choices": [
            "purchase",
            "insulate",
            "persuade",
            "propose"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "persuade"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wildlife ............ is necessary to stop species from dying out .",
        "choices": [
            "pressure",
            "livestock",
            "intelligence",
            "conservation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "conservation"
    },
    {
        "question": "............. are not paid for the work they do.",
        "choices": [
            "Founders",
            "Volunteers",
            "Conservationists",
            "Teenagers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Volunteers"
    },
    {
        "question": "He ............ all other runners and won the race.",
        "choices": [
            "ran past",
            "researched",
            "grew up",
            "reduced"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ran past"
    },
    {
        "question": "His ............ is so low that he has to look for a second job.",
        "choices": [
            "compassion",
            "documentary",
            "income",
            "task"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "income"
    },
    {
        "question": "I look forward to returning to my ............ of Assuit where I was born and educated.",
        "choices": [
            "workplace",
            "hometown",
            "track",
            "support"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "hometown"
    },
    {
        "question": "As a striker, you are supposed to ............ goals, not to lose the ball.",
        "choices": [
            "miss",
            "realise",
            "reach",
            "score"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "score"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tourism ............ national income .",
        "choices": [
            "aim",
            "aims",
            "benefit",
            "benefits"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "benefits"
    },
    {
        "question": "As a ............ , he has great interest in looking after the environment.",
        "choices": [
            "founder",
            "volunteer",
            "conservationist",
            "teenager"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "conservationist"
    },
    {
        "question": "I feel ............ for the old and the sick.",
        "choices": [
            "compassion",
            "documentary",
            "income",
            "task"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "compassion"
    },
    {
        "question": "I think I won't ............ Rokaya. She was a little child when I last saw her 20 years ago.",
        "choices": [
            "reduce",
            "aim",
            "recognize",
            "transplant"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "recognize"
    },
    {
        "question": "She pays ............ visits to her old grandma in Suez.",
        "choices": [
            "safe",
            "charitable",
            "regular",
            "missing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "regular"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will lend you the money even if I know you don't have the ............ to pay it back.",
        "choices": [
            "able",
            "ability",
            "inability",
            "disability"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "inability"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mr Mohammed gave each student a/an ............ to do.",
        "choices": [
            "compassion",
            "documentary",
            "income",
            "task"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "task"
    },
    {
        "question": "My uncle is one of the ............ of this charity. They started it in 1998.",
        "choices": [
            "founders",
            "volunteers",
            "conservationists",
            "teenagers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "founders"
    },
    {
        "question": "When I ............ , I hope I will be able to help myself and my community.",
        "choices": [
            "run past",
            "research",
            "grow up",
            "respect"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "respect"
    },
    {
        "question": "A/An ............ is a strong hope or wish.",
        "choices": [
            "desire",
            "track",
            "will",
            "ability"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "desire"
    },
    {
        "question": "To ............ is to allow some blood or a body organ to be removed from your body so that it can be used in a hospital to help someone who is ill or injured.",
        "choices": [
            "reduce",
            "protect",
            "score",
            "donate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donate"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ means willing to give money, spend time etc., in order to help people or give them pleasure.",
        "choices": [
            "Intelligent",
            "Responsible",
            "Generous",
            "Safe"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Generous"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ means continuing for a long period of time, or relating to what will happen in the distant future.",
        "choices": [
            "Short-term",
            "Long-term",
            "Forever",
            "For good"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Long-term"
    },
    {
        "question": "A ............ is someone whose behavior, attitudes, etc. people try to copy because they admire them.",
        "choices": [
            "donor",
            "biologist",
            "roleplay",
            "role model"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "role model"
    },
    {
        "question": "........... is the respect and admiration that someone or something gets because of their success or important position in society.",
        "choices": [
            "Prestige",
            "Generosity",
            "Support",
            "Ability"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Prestige"
    },
    {
        "question": "A/An ............ is an official document that people sign to show that they have agreed to something.",
        "choices": [
            "admiration",
            "agreement",
            "pressure",
            "donation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "agreement"
    },
    {
        "question": "A ............ means a deep, loud noise made by an animal such as a lion, or by someone's voice.",
        "choices": [
            "success",
            "killing",
            "roar",
            "livestock"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "roar"
    }
]